buykorea.org 2010-10-31

# Privacy Policy | Buykorea Help Desk - Search Privacy Policy from Buykorea

|  |   
---|---  
|  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  | [Notice](javascript:GoListPage\('/buykorea/front_eng/cs/SCS0301LS.jsp','001','&p_menu_id=0104&menu_id=010401'\);)  
---  
[FAQ](javascript:GoListPage\('/buykorea/front_eng/cs/SCS0401LS.jsp','002','&cs_menu_id=ALL&p_menu_id=0104&menu_id=010402'\);)  
[Offer.Buyer](javascript:GoListPage\('/buykorea/front_eng/cs/SCS0401LS.jsp','002','&cs_menu_id=144&p_menu_id=0104&menu_id=010402'\);)  
[Foreign Markets](javascript:GoListPage\('/buykorea/front_eng/cs/SCS0401LS.jsp','002','&cs_menu_id=145&p_menu_id=0104&menu_id=010402'\);)  
[Trader's Club](javascript:GoListPage\('/buykorea/front_eng/cs/SCS0401LS.jsp','002','&cs_menu_id=148&p_menu_id=0104&menu_id=010402'\);)  
[Search](javascript:GoListPage\('/buykorea/front_eng/cs/SCS0401LS.jsp','002','&cs_menu_id=149&p_menu_id=0104&menu_id=010402'\);)  
[Member's Info](javascript:GoListPage\('/buykorea/front_eng/cs/SCS0401LS.jsp','002','&cs_menu_id=150&p_menu_id=0104&menu_id=010402'\);)  
[Etc](javascript:GoListPage\('/buykorea/front_eng/cs/SCS0401LS.jsp','002','&cs_menu_id=151&p_menu_id=0104&menu_id=010402'\);)  
[Questions & Answers](javascript:GoListPage\('/buykorea/front_eng/cs/SCS0501LS.jsp','003','&cs_menu_id=ALL&p_menu_id=0104&menu_id=010403'\);)  
[Q&A Board](javascript:GoListPage\('/buykorea/front_eng/cs/SCS0501LS.jsp','003','&cs_menu_id=ALL&p_menu_id=0104&menu_id=010403'\);)  
E-Mail  
User Agreement  
Privacy Policy  
|   
---  
Enhance Your Business Scope with BUYKOREA  
**   Privacy Policy**  
---  
   
**We, as a government-run agency, never sell or rent your personal information to third parties for the marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Please read this privacy policy with care to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. We want you to fully understand our privacy practices and Privacy Policy.  
If you have additional questions, you may send email to admin@buykorea.org**  
   
| ****| **Overview**  
---|---  
  | The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and subdomains of www.buykorea.org (the "Site") and apply generally to our subsidiaries or joint venture websites whose specific privacy policies are available. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Site. 

This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services, we collect from you and what may happen to that information. Although this policy may seem long, we have prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make informed decisions. All of our subsidiaries and joint ventures operate under similar privacy practices as described in this Privacy Policy and, subject to the requirements of applicable law, we strive to provide a consistent set of privacy practices.

By accepting the Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon visiting the site for all users.   

  |    
****| **Table of Contents**  
  |  **1\. Information We Collect  
2\. Our Use of Your Information   
3\. Our Disclosure of Your Information   
4\. Control of Your Password   
5\. Security   
6\. Notice **  
  |    
  | **1\. Information We Collect**  
  | Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. 

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature. 

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the Site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the Site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. 

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site. 

If you establish a credit account with us to pay the fees we charge, we collect some additional information, such as a billing address, a credit card number and a credit card expiration date and tracking information from checks or money orders.  

  |    
  |  **2\. Our Use of Your Information**  
  | We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request. We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to: resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote safe trading; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy. 

If you choose to list an item for sale on the Site or open a credit account, or otherwise provide us with your financial information, we use your address and billing information to bill you and provide associated support. 

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site. 

You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications on the notification preferences page. You may make changes to your notification preferences at any time.   
  
  |    
  | **3\. Our Disclosure of Your Information**  
  | As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide our services.   
Legal Requests. as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you from bad actors. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, telephone number, email address. We will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to.  
  |    
  |  **4\. Control of Your Password**  
  | You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password, including fees charged to your account. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your password to any third parties. If you choose to share your User ID and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.  
  |    
  | **5\. Security**  
  | Your information is stored on our servers. We use procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption, "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.   
  |    
  |  **6\. Notice**  
  | We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amend terms on the Site. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site.
